George W. Henry Foundation and the Canon Clinton Jones Archive 1933-1986 (bulk 1963-1986) GLBTQ.2010.01
GLBTQ Archives, Central Connecticut State University
- Series II: Canon Clinton Jones Papers
  - Human Rights and Opportunities, Jones, Clingon, Remarks before the committee on Human Rights... of the Connecticut general Assembly... on Civil Rights for all persons regardless of sexual orientation, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Integrity Convention, Chicago, IL, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Integrity Convention, San Francisco, CA, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Integrity Convention, 1978, Minneapolis, MN (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Integrity Convention, Denver, CO, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Integrity Convention, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Integrity Convention, New York, NY, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Integrity/Hartford Announcements, January 7, 1981 - August 23, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Integrity. 13 Questions About..., Membership Application, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Joint Commission on the Church in the Human Affairs, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Jones, Clinton R. A Counseling Ministry, an Overview, Nov. 4, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Jones, Clinton R. Formation of a Transsexual Group, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Jones, Clinton R. A Statement of Transsexualism, undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Jones, Clinton R. View Point Concerning the Seduction of Children, January 26, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Kalos Society, Hartford, 1970's (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Lesbian Feminist Writing and Publishing, ed. by Beth Hodges in Margins, August, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Mattachine New York, Florida, and Washington, D.C., Chapters, Brochures, and Flyers, 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Memoirs of an Ancient Activist by Paul Goodman in Win, November 1969 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Men's Liberation by Eric Bently, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Minnesota Council For the Church & The Homophile Articles and Bibliography, 1970's (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Must the Homosexual be Rejected? by Harry Benjamin, Homosexuality Conflicting Theories, by Isadore Rubing, Homosexuality in Women, by Edward Dengrove, 1957, 1960, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - One Incorporated Flyers, Catalogs Annual Report, 1959-1969 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Pittenger, Norman, Copy of Letter to Rev. Paul Moore, June 18, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Playboy Philosophy, 12 Issues, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Report of the [Connecticut] Diocesan Commission on Marriage and Human Sexuality, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Roger Dean Homosexual Completely Delivered, Greatest Is Love, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Ross, Kenneth N. Letter to a Homosexual, With Handwritten Comments, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Salvatorian Gay Ministry Task Force, "A Model for Ministry to the Homosexual Community", March, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - San Francisco, Report on Conditions in the Tenderloin District, February, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Seabury Book: Folder of correspondence, reviews, and articles concerning Clinton Jones' book, Understanding Gay Relatives and Friends, 1977-1981 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Sex Education and the American Democratic Process, Siecus Newsletter, April, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Sexual Morality in "Pastoral Psychology", November, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Should Homosexuality be in the APA Nomenclature? A Symposium, American Journal of Psychiatry, November, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Society for Individual Rights (Sir), Application Form, undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - State General of the Netherlands, Withdrawal of Article 248 of the Penal Code, Abolishing Penal Provision Concerning Homosexuals, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Study Units 1-4: 1. Created as Sexual beings, 2. churches role in developing moral values 3. The Family What is it..., undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Terwilliger, Robert Copy of Letter to Rev. Thomas F. Pike, October 3, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Transsexualism, 1974; undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
    1. The Nature and Treatment of Transsexualism by Harry Benjamin, M.D., and Charles L. Ihlenfeld, M.D.
    2. Of Sex Reassignment: 2 Men Who Would Be Women, by Ira B. Pauly, M.D.
    3. Mary In The Lavender Pumps, by Joyce Wadler
    4. Suggested Reading
    5. Corbett v. Corbett (otherwise Ashley)
    6. The Sexes, Time, Jan. 21, 1974
    7. Transsexualism, by Sue Jane Wilson
    8. Various other articles on Transsexualism
  - Transsexual the Hardest Decisions, Correspondence and articles, Confide Personal Counseling Services, 1974-1977 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Transsexualism, undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Transsexuals [Articles, Pamphlets, Brochures], 1967-1988 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Transsexualism, 1974-1989 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    1. Articles, 1974 - 1989
    2. Jones, Clinton R. A statement of Transsexualism
    3. Jones Clinton R. Formation of a Transsexual Group, 1975
    4. XX Club Chapter and Constitution, 1978
    5. Organizational bylaws of the XX Club, Hartford, 1976
    6. Jones, Clinton R. A counseling Ministry, "An Overview" [1985]
    7. Gold, Louis H. Origin and function of the Gender Identity Clinic of New England, [1972]
  - Transsexualism Correspondence, January 1976 - December 1979 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - XX Club, Hartford, 1980-1984 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - XX Club, Hartford, December 1974 - December 1979 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - XX Club, Hartford, 1985-1987 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Understanding Homosexuality, George W. Henry Foundation, Hartford [brochure], undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - What About Homosexuality? in Social Progress, November/December 1967 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - What About Homosexuality, Thomas Nelson, Inc., correspondence, reviews, articles, 1971-1981 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - York, Richard H. An Open Letter to the Church [copy], Mar. 25, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - American Association of Sex Educators, Counselors, and Therapists (AASECT), undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Archbishop of Canterbury, Dr. Rowan Williams, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Brown, Keith; "Annals of Gay Spirit", typescript, 143 pp., 1997 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Children From the Shadows 9, Conference, March 22-23, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Gender Identity Clinic Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Gender Identity Clinic Correspondence, 1978-1983 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Gender Identity Clinic Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Gender Identity Clinic Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Harry Benjamin International Dysphoria Association, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Harry Benjamin International Gender Dysphoria, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - House of Bishops Report of the Theology Committee, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Integrity/Hartford Correspondence, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Integrity/Hartford Correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Integrity/Hartford Correspondence, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Integrity/Hartford Correspondence, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Integrity/Hartford Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - International Foundation for Gender Education, Trinity Award, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - International Symposium on Gender Dyshporia, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Love Makes a Family, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Articles, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - National Directory of Facilities & Services for Lesbian and Gay Alcoholics, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Open Letter to Religous Leaders About Sex Education, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Smith, Andrew D., Episcopal Diocese of Connecticut (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Transexualism Correspondence, 1975-1979 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Transexualism Correspondence, 1980-1987 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Transexualism-- Papers, articles, etc..., undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Transexualism-- Papers, newsletters, pamphlets, brochures, etc..., undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Transexualism-- Papers, newsletters, etc..., undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Vatican Ban on Transsexuals Being Priests, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - 5th International Symposium on Gender Dysphoria, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - 6th International Symposium on Gender Dysphoria, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - 7th International Symposium on Gender Dysphoria, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - 8th International Symposium on Gender Dysphoria, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - 9th International Symposium on Gender Dysphoria, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - 10th International Symposium on Gender Dysphoria, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - 13th International Symposium on Gender Dysphoria, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Christ Church Cathedral First annual dinner in honor of the Rev. Canon Clinton Jones, November 12, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - 30th Anniversary Celebration – Committee on Sexual Minorities and Dedication George W. Henry Library at CCSU, December 12, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Death of Canon Clinton, Obituary, articles, June 3, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Doubleday, William A. Rev. Sermon Preached at the Thanksgiving Eucharist for the Life of the Reverend Canon Clinton R. Jones. - Christ Church Cathedral, June 7, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 40)